readyphotosite.com 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy - Ready Photo Site Flash Photography Websites

Ready Photo Site is committed to protecting your privacy. We have developed this privacy policy to inform you about what information this web site collects, how we may use it and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties.

The Policy Policy applies to all personally identifiable information collected by Ready Photo Site website and other country-specific Ready Photo Site websites owned by Ready Photo Site.com.

**Information We Collect**

Ready Photo Site.com automatically collects such non-personal information as the third party website (the website that referred you to us), your IP address, browser type and language you are using, and the time of your visit. We also collect navigational information, including the information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other activities you perform while visiting our website. 

In case you provide us with your demographic information (e.g., your occupation, hobbies, gender, or interests) it is collected as your personal information. 

We only collect your personal information with your permission. By voluntarily providing your personal information to us, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Our definition of personally identifiable information includes information you provide if you wish to purchase our products, including your name, billing address, email address, and phone number.

Please note: we do not collect the credit card information, because we use payment gateways to process your order(s). 

You may always choose not to provide your personal information to us, but if you choose so, the offered products and services may not be available to you.

**Use of Your Personal Information**

Ready Photo Site collects and uses your personal information to: 

  * * process your transactions;
  * * provide customer service;
  * * perform survey/research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies;
  * * display content that is customized to your interests and preferences;
  * * run contests, select entrants, and choose prize winners;
  * * communicate with you about your transactions (we may send transaction-related communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, and purchase confirmations);
  * *provide you promotional information about our new products, services, and other offers you may be interested in.

**Information Disclosure**

As stated in this Privacy Policy, Ready Photo Site does not disclose or sell your personal information to any third-parties.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of Ready Photo Site.com. For example, we may hire other companies to process payments, host websites, carry out orders and shipments, to provide data storage and marketing assistance, to conduct audits, etc. The third-party service providers (i) only obtain the personal information they need to provide the service, (ii) agree to use it according to our Privacy Policy, and (iii) are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. 

We reserve to ourselves the right to disclose your personal information if required and permitted to do so by law.

**Security of Your Personal Information**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect your personal information including: 

  * * limiting the access to your personal information to those of our employees who need it to provide services to you;
  * * requiring employees to sign non-disclosure agreements to protect customer's personal information and other confidential information;
  * * ensuring that third-party service providers sign non-disclosure agreements to maintain confidentiality of your personal information and not to use it for any unauthorized purposes;
  * * storing your personal information in secure computer systems which protect it from unauthorized access or use.

Please be advised, however, that no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We reserve to ourselves the right to amend the terms of this privacy policy at any time. The date of the recent amendment will be posted at the top of the Privacy Policy page. If there are any changes in this section of Policy Privacy or the section on the Use of Your Personal Information, we will notify you by either sending you an email, posting a notice on Policy Privacy page or on our home page. We encourage you to check our Policy Privacy page for updates each time you visit our websites. 

****
